FORREST MILLS

Full-Stack Software Developer

mills_forrest@yahoo.com

) (830)-928-3262

in LinkedIn

Github

San Antonio, TX

CAREER OBJECTIVE

My goal as a full-stack developer is to build capable, reliable, and installable applications. I desire to refine my skills and continue to learn as much as I can. I recently earned a certificate from the University of Texas-San Antonio in full-stack development. I have experience in agile environments and responsibilities in front and back-end tasks.

WORK EXPERIENCE

RSC Rep IV

Charter Communications

iii October 2015 - October 2021

- San Antonio, TX
- Coordinate and manage quota moves to meet service level agreements.
- Formulated quota reports, move reports, and forecasted connect activity based on demand, special projects, and marketing forecasts.
- Managed field operations scheduling and workforce management.
- Managed the creation and maintenance of technician skill sets.

Dispatcher V

Charter Communications

🛗 October 2015 - November 2016

- San Antonio, TX
- Managed and dispatched teams of technicians and ensured timeframes were met. Moved work between teams of technicians.
- Provided technical support via phone for all residential services.
- · Processed, scheduled, and corrected work orders.

Technical Support Rep II

Charter Communications

iii October 2014 - October 2015

- San Antonio, TX
- Provided customer care and technical support for all residential services.
- Managed de-escalation of customer escalations.

Technical Support Rep II

Volt

- iii January 1 October 2014
- San Antonio, TX
- Provided customer care & technical support for all residential services.
- Diagnose chronic issues, created escalation tickets, followed up on final resolutions.

SKILLS

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

React.js

Node.js

MongoDB

Rest APIs

Mongoose.js

Express.js

jQuery

GraphQL

MERN Stack

MySQL

Jest.js

npm

EDUCATION

A.S.

Computer Science

Northeast Lakeview College

- iii October 2018 current
- San Antonio, TX

CERTIFICATIONS

Full Stack Web Developer Certification (10/2021 - 04/2022)